acellus.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy

This policy describes how we treat personal information when you use services offered by Acellus on Acellus.com.

**How we collect information about you**  
When you visit Acellus.com, we may collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website.

When you sign up for an Account, we ask for your personal information so that we can provide you with the service. The information we require at the time of registration may include your name, address, phone number, email address, payment information, and applicable student information.

When you subscribe to services offered by Acellus, we collect information about each transaction, including the transaction amount, a description of the services being purchased, the name of the buyer, and the type of payment used. We may also collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes.

In order to protect you from fraud or other misconduct, we may obtain information about you from third parties to verify the information you provide. For example, we may use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your credit or debit card information and address match the information that you provided to us.

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

**How we use cookies**  
When you access our website, we, or companies we hire to track how our website is used, may place small data files called “cookies” on your computer.

We may send a “session cookie” to your computer when you log in to your account. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we don’t need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect.

We may also use longer-lasting cookies for other purposes such as to display your e-mail address on our sign-in form, so that you don’t need to retype the e-mail address each time you log in to your account. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website.

**How we protect and store personal information**  
We store and process your personal information on our computers in the US, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls, data encryption, and multi-factor authentication for login; we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files; and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.

**Personal information provided about children**  
We understand that our student users who are under 13 years of age need special safeguards and privacy protection, and it is our intent to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Acellus does not collect personal information from children online at any point. Acellus only receives personal information about your children directly from you (or the child’s school) when the children are enrolled into Acellus. You can review certain personal information that Acellus has regarding your children online by signing in to the Acellus Parent Interface. Please be aware that some personal information relating to your children’s educational records may not be able to be disclosed by Acellus due to state and/or Federal law.

**How we use the personal information we collect**  
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience.

We may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * process transactions and send notices about your transactions;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;
  * customize, measure, and improve our services, the content and layout of our website; and
  * compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.

**How we share personal information with other parties**  
We may share your personal information with:

  * Companies that we plan to merge with or be acquired by. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information could be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.)
  * Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when 
    * we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure;
    * we need to do so to comply with law; or
    * we believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our User Agreement.
  * Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.

Acellus will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.

**Changes to this policy**  
We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. We last modified this Policy on February 27, 2015.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please [contact us](https://www.acellus.com/contact_us.php) through our website or by writing to us at Acellus Academy, Attn: Privacy Department, 26900 E. Pink Hill Rd., Independence, MO 64057.

**Copyright**  
If you are the owner of content that is being used in an Acellus course without your permission, then you may request the content be removed from Acellus by contacting our designated agent. We will, of course, need some evidence to support your claim of ownership.
